<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Welcome to My Cybersecurity Portfolio on CyberSec Portfolio</title><link>https://darklink2151.github.io/cybersec-portfolio/</link><description>Recent content in Welcome to My Cybersecurity Portfolio on CyberSec Portfolio</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://darklink2151.github.io/cybersec-portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://darklink2151.github.io/cybersec-portfolio/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://darklink2151.github.io/cybersec-portfolio/about/</guid><description>Security Researcher &amp;amp; Ethical Hacker I am a cybersecurity enthusiast with a passion for penetration testing, vulnerability research, and ethical hacking. My expertise includes:
Network Security Assessment Web Application Security Binary Exploitation Reverse Engineering Social Engineering Digital Forensics Technical Skills Programming Languages: Python, Bash, C/C++, PowerShell Security Tools: Metasploit, Burp Suite, Wireshark, Nmap, Ghidra Operating Systems: Kali Linux, Windows, macOS Cloud Security: AWS, Azure, GCP Certifications: OSCP, CEH, Security+ Hardware Setup Motherboard: ASRock X570 Taichi CPU: AMD Ryzen 7 5700X GPUs: ASRock 6600 Challenger (display) Zotac 3050 (computational tasks) OS: Kali Linux Contact GitHub: Your GitHub Profile LinkedIn: Your LinkedIn Profile Email: your.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started with Kali Linux</title><link>https://darklink2151.github.io/cybersec-portfolio/posts/kali-linux-setup/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://darklink2151.github.io/cybersec-portfolio/posts/kali-linux-setup/</guid><description>Getting Started with Kali Linux This post covers the basics of setting up Kali Linux for security testing.</description></item><item><title>HackTheBox: Lame Walkthrough</title><link>https://darklink2151.github.io/cybersec-portfolio/ctf/htb-lame/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://darklink2151.github.io/cybersec-portfolio/ctf/htb-lame/</guid><description>HackTheBox: Lame Walkthrough This is a walkthrough of the &amp;ldquo;Lame&amp;rdquo; machine from HackTheBox, one of the simplest machines on the platform.</description></item><item><title>Network Scanner Tool</title><link>https://darklink2151.github.io/cybersec-portfolio/projects/network-scanner/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://darklink2151.github.io/cybersec-portfolio/projects/network-scanner/</guid><description>Network Scanner Tool A Python-based network scanner for identifying open ports and services on target systems.</description></item></channel></rss>